<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Traffic on Open Data Hub - Develop digital solutions based on real data</title>
    <link>https://example.com/datatype/traffic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Traffic on Open Data Hub - Develop digital solutions based on real data</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://example.com/datatype/traffic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bluetooth Traffic Sensors</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/bluetooth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/bluetooth/</guid>
      <description>Experimental Bluetooth-based sensors and detectors. Currently located in Bolzano and Merano (soon in other locations of South Tyrol, such as Merano) and A22. Gathered data are then processed to obtain useful information about the traffic, such as total number of vehicles detected and an estimation of heavy and light vehicles.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v2 Swagger URL https://mobility.api.opendatahub.bz.it/ StationType BluetoothStation Sources CISMA OpenData Open Data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Air Quality</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/environment/</guid>
      <description>Pollution and Air Quality data (such as CO, NO2, PM 2.5, PM10&amp;hellip;). Partly manually elaborated data to increase data quality. Open Data with longer time frame. Additional restricted data with smaller time frame (only for expert knowledge).
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v2 Swagger URL https://mobility.api.opendatahub.bz.it/ StationType EnvironmentStation Sources APPA Bolzano, APPA Trento, Municipality of Bolzano, A22 OpenData EnvironmentStation data from A22 is partially closed data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parking</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/parking/</guid>
      <description>Parking stations - off street parking data (Bolzano, Merano, Trento, Rovereto). Slot availability and predictions. Parking sensors - on street parking data (Bolzano, soon Merano). Single parking slots on streets, can be within a virtual area.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v2 Swagger URL https://mobility.api.opendatahub.bz.it/ StationType ParkingStation, ParkingSensor Sources Municipality of Bolzano, Merano, Trento and Rovereto, A22 OpenData ParkingSensor data is open data. ParkingStation data is partially closed data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RWIS Station</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/rwisstation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/rwisstation/</guid>
      <description>The Road Weather stations are sensors that measure both the road surface and the weather conditions. A22 (Modena - Brennero): restricted to a project
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v2 Swagger URL https://mobility.api.opendatahub.bz.it/ StationType RWISstation Sources A22 OpenData RWISstation data is partially closed data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Station</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/trafficstation_one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/trafficstation_one/</guid>
      <description>This dataset contains data collected by sensors along the Italian A22 motorway and municipality of Bolzano, such as, real time (A22) and aggregated data recorded by sensors drowned in asphalt, cameras, radar, other sensors.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v2 Swagger URL https://mobility.api.opendatahub.bz.it/ StationType TrafficSensor, Trafficstation Sources Municipality of Bolzano, A22 OpenData Data is partially closed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Velocity Sensors</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/linkstation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/linkstation/</guid>
      <description>Data processing of experimental Bluetooth-based sensors and detectors (A22 data based on Telepass). Gathered data are processed to obtain the estimated travel time and speed of the vehicles.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v2 Swagger URL https://mobility.api.opendatahub.bz.it/ StationType LinkStation Sources A22, NOI OpenData LinkStation data is partially closed data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weather</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/weather/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/weather/</guid>
      <description>This dataset contains meteorological data provided by the hydrographical Department of South Tyrol and Trentino, such as Precipitation and Air temperature. Here are the measurements of the weather data, not the forecast.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v2 Swagger URL https://mobility.api.opendatahub.bz.it/ StationType MeteoStation Sources Department of South Tyrol and Trentino OpenData MeteoStation data is partially closed data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Variable Message Sign</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/trafficstation_two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/trafficstation_two/</guid>
      <description>The VMS (Variable Message Sign) sensors collect data about the electronic road signs on the A22 motorway.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v2 Swagger URL https://mobility.api.opendatahub.bz.it/ StationType VMS Sources A22 OpenData Data only available to authorized collaborators </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
