<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Open Data Hub - Develop digital solutions based on real data</title>
    <link>https://example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Open Data Hub - Develop digital solutions based on real data</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Articles</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/article/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/article/</guid>
      <description>This dataset contains articles such as recipes, books, catalogues, guides about South Tyrol. It contains Historical data. Only recipes are still updated.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v1 Swagger URL http://tourism.opendatahub.bz.it/swagger/index.html#/Article Sources IDM Content data (data from 2010 to 2016, recipes still up-to-date) and NOI OpenData Open Data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bike Counter</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/mobility/bikecounter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/mobility/bikecounter/</guid>
      <description>This dataset contains data of the bike counter service in Bolzano.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v2 s Swagger URL https://mobility.api.opendatahub.bz.it/ StationType VehicleDetetection(count) Sources Municipality of Bolzano (FAMAS System) OpenData Open Data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bikesharing</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/mobility/bikesharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/mobility/bikesharing/</guid>
      <description>This dataset contains data of the bike sharing service in Bolzano and Merano, such as stations (for station based service - Bolzano), areas (for free floating service - Merano), availability, battery state, etc&amp;hellip;
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v2 Swagger URL {https://mobility.api.opendatahub.bz.it/ StationType Bicycle, Bicyclestationbay, BikesharingStation Sources Municipality of Bolzano and Merano OpenData Open Data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bluetooth Traffic Sensors</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/bluetooth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/bluetooth/</guid>
      <description>Experimental Bluetooth-based sensors and detectors. Currently located in Bolzano and Merano (soon in other locations of South Tyrol, such as Merano) and A22. Gathered data are then processed to obtain useful information about the traffic, such as total number of vehicles detected and an estimation of heavy and light vehicles.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v2 Swagger URL https://mobility.api.opendatahub.bz.it/ StationType BluetoothStation Sources CISMA OpenData Open Data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carpooling</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/mobility/carpooling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/mobility/carpooling/</guid>
      <description>This dataset contains all data of the carpooling service of the Burggrafenamt/ Burgraviato, such as carpooling users (users express consent to privacy, no sensitive data is exchanged), locations and available destinations and availability.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v2 Swagger URL https://mobility.api.opendatahub.bz.it/ StationType CarpoolingHub, CarpoolingService, CarpoolingUser Sources Bezirksgemeinschaft Burggrafenamt/Burgraviato, Inno.vìe OpenData Open Data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carsharing</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/mobility/carsharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/mobility/carsharing/</guid>
      <description>This dataset contains all data of the carsharing service in South Tyrol, such as stations and availability.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v2 Swagger URL https://mobility.api.opendatahub.bz.it/ StationType CarsharingStation Sources Car Sharing Südtirol Alto Adige OpenData Open Data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creative Industries</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/otherdomains/creativeindustries/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/otherdomains/creativeindustries/</guid>
      <description>This dataset originates from data collected in the DAVINCI project, whose aim is to increase local businesses by improving innovation and digitalisation of services. The data consists of a list of actors who operate in the creativity sector in South Tyrol and is used as data source to generate a map for a dedicated Web Component, available in Open Data Hub’s Web Component Store.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v2 Swagger URL https://mobility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Browser</title>
      <link>https://example.com/quickstart/data-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/quickstart/data-browser/</guid>
      <description>Browse and discover the available data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>District &amp; Municipalities</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/locationandcommon_three/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/locationandcommon_three/</guid>
      <description>In particular, these datasets contain Districts, Municipalities which are provided by LTS. And, in addition Areas are a LTS Categorization (custom LTS cluster). Areas, for example, are used on LTS Activities.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v1 Swagger URL https://tourism.opendatahub.bz.it/swagger/index.html#/Common/get_v1_Municipality https://tourism.opendatahub.bz.it/swagger/index.html#/Common/get_v1_District Sources LTS OpenData Open Data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Echarging station</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/mobility/echargingstation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/mobility/echargingstation/</guid>
      <description>This dataset exposes data about the existing e-charging stations and plugs in South Tyrol and their availability status, including historical data and usage. Hydrogen station data are included.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v2 Swagger URL https://mobility.api.opendatahub.bz.it/ StationType EChargingPlug, EChargingStation Sources Alperia (Neogy), Route220, nevicam, Driwe, H2 Südtirol Alto Adige OpenData Open Data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events NOI &amp; EURAC</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/eventshort/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/eventshort/</guid>
      <description>This dataset contains events provided by NOI Techpark and Eurac.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v1 Swagger URL https://tourism.opendatahub.bz.it/swagger/index.html#/EventShort Sources NOI Techpark and Eurac OpenData Open Data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Locations</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/locationandcommon_one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/locationandcommon_one/</guid>
      <description>These datasets contain Location &amp;amp; Commons Data API of Tourism Regions of South Tyrol. ID Lists of Regions, Tourism Associations, Areas, Municipalities, Ski Areas. Data provided by IDM.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v1 Swagger URL http://tourism.opendatahub.bz.it/swagger/index.html#/Common http://tourism.opendatahub.bz.it/swagger/index.html#/Location Sources IDM OpenData Open Data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NOI Place</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/otherdomains/noiplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/otherdomains/noiplace/</guid>
      <description>This dataset contains all places, offices, meeting rooms, and in general all points of interest located in the various buildings that compose the NOI Techpark in Bolzano, Italy. This dataset is used to create the interactive map of the NOI Techpark.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v2 Swagger URL https://mobility.api.opendatahub.bz.it/ StationType NOI-Place Sources NOI Techpark OpenData Open Data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snow Report</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/snowreport/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/snowreport/</guid>
      <description>Snow Report Data dataset contains detailed report of all South Tyrolean Ski Areas. Lifts, Slopes, Ski tracks, Sledges (status and conditions) data provided by LTS (daily updated), Measuring points (snow height, last snow day) data provided by LTS (daily updated), Ski Areas basic data provided by IDM.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v1 Swagger URL https://tourism.opendatahub.bz.it/swagger/index.html#/Weather/get_v1_Weather_SnowReport Sources Snow data provided by LTS / Ski Areas basic data provided by IDM OpenData Open Data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tourism Regions</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/locationandcommon_two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/locationandcommon_two/</guid>
      <description>In particular, these datasets contain Regions Data, Tourism Associations, Meta Regions, Ski Regions, Ski Areas, Experience Areas are the IDM clusters for South Tyrol Tourism Regions.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v1 Swagger URL http://tourism.opendatahub.bz.it/swagger/index.html#/Common http://tourism.opendatahub.bz.it/swagger/index.html#/Location Sources IDM OpenData Open Data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weather Forecast</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/weatherforecast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/weatherforecast/</guid>
      <description>South Tyrolean Weather Information general. Updated at 07:00 and 11:00. South Tyrolean Weather Details for today, tomorrow, Mountain weather today, tomorrow, Station weather today, tomorrow and 5 days evolution. All data is requested live through the Weather service of the province BZ. Data available in languages de, it, en.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v1 Swagger URL http://tourism.opendatahub.bz.it/swagger/index.html#/Weather Sources SIAG OpenData Open Data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accommodations</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/accommodation_one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/accommodation_one/</guid>
      <description>This dataset contains accommodations in South Tyrol. Accessible via REST or the AlpineBits HotelData open standard.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json, XML AlpineBits API version v1, AlpineBits HotelData 2017-10, 2018-10, 2020-10 Swagger URL https://tourism.opendatahub.bz.it/swagger/ui/index#/Accommodation AlpineBits URL https://alpinebits.opendatahub.bz.it/AlpineBits Sources Data provided by LTS OpenData Accommodations data is partially closed data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activities</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/activitiesandpois_three/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/activitiesandpois_three/</guid>
      <description>This dataset contains data about activities from LTS API (LTS ActivityData), IDM and Dolomiti Superski such as local tours, hiking, running &amp;amp; fitness, cross-country skiing, alpine climbing, e-bike, downhill, nordic walking, etc. This dataset offers LTS categorization and enhanced filtering.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v1 Swagger URL https://tourism.opendatahub.bz.it/swagger/index.html#/ODHActivityPoi/get_v1_ODHActivityPoi Sources LTS ActivityData, IDM, Dolomiti Superski OpenData Activities data from IDM and Dolomiti Superski is open data. Data from LTS is partially closed data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activities, Pois &amp; Gastronomy</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/activitiesandpois_one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/activitiesandpois_one/</guid>
      <description>This dataset contains a collection of activities and points of interest (PoI) and gastronomy locations (such as restaurants, bars, alpine huts, etc.) in the South Tyrol region. The available data have been extracted from different sources such as SIAG South Tyrolean museums, Südtirol Wein, Dolomiti Superski, LTS, IDM created content.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v1 Swagger URL http://tourism.opendatahub.bz.it/swagger/index.html#/ODHActivityPoi Sources LTS ActivityData, LTS PoiData, LTS GastronomicData, SuedtirolWein, SIAG Museum data, IDM Content and Dolomiti Superski OpenData Data from SuedtirolWein, SIAG, IDM and Dolomiti Superski is Open Data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Air Quality</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/environment/</guid>
      <description>Pollution and Air Quality data (such as CO, NO2, PM 2.5, PM10&amp;hellip;). Partly manually elaborated data to increase data quality. Open Data with longer time frame. Additional restricted data with smaller time frame (only for expert knowledge).
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v2 Swagger URL https://mobility.api.opendatahub.bz.it/ StationType EnvironmentStation Sources APPA Bolzano, APPA Trento, Municipality of Bolzano, A22 OpenData EnvironmentStation data from A22 is partially closed data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analytics Tool</title>
      <link>https://example.com/quickstart/analytics-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/quickstart/analytics-tool/</guid>
      <description>Find out information about sensors and their locations and measure (near-real time data).​</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/events/</guid>
      <description>This dataset contains active events provided by LTS (TIC Web), DRIN and TreviLab such as meetings, fairs, markets, performances, courses, music, festivals, hikes, trips, guided tours, exhibitions, etc. It includes past events.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v1 Swagger URL http://tourism.opendatahub.bz.it/swagger/index.html#/Event Sources LTS, DRIN, TreviLab OpenData Events data from LTS is partially closed data. Data from DRIN and TreviLab is open data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gastronomy</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/activitiesandpois_four/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/activitiesandpois_four/</guid>
      <description>This dataset contains data about gastronomy locations from LTS API (LTS GastronomyData), SuedtirolWein and IDM such as restaurants, bars, bistros, pubs, apres ski, pizzerias, fast food, cafeterias, vinotheques, beer gardens, mountain refuges, alpine huts, ski huts, etc. This dataset offers enhance filtering (cuisine types, ceremony codes, dish codes etc.)
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v1 Swagger URL https://tourism.opendatahub.bz.it/swagger/index.html#/ODHActivityPoi/get_v1_ODHActivityPoi Sources IDM, SuedtirolWein, LTS OpenData Gastronomy data from IDM and SuedtirolWein is open data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parking</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/parking/</guid>
      <description>Parking stations - off street parking data (Bolzano, Merano, Trento, Rovereto). Slot availability and predictions. Parking sensors - on street parking data (Bolzano, soon Merano). Single parking slots on streets, can be within a virtual area.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v2 Swagger URL https://mobility.api.opendatahub.bz.it/ StationType ParkingStation, ParkingSensor Sources Municipality of Bolzano, Merano, Trento and Rovereto, A22 OpenData ParkingSensor data is open data. ParkingStation data is partially closed data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Points Of Interests</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/activitiesandpois_two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/activitiesandpois_two/</guid>
      <description>This dataset contains data about PoIs from LTS API (LTS PoiData), such as beauty and wellness, bikes, castles, climbing halls, cocktail bars, e-bike rentals, fashion shops, pharmacies, gas stations, car parks, shops, ski schools, etc. This dataset offers LTS categorization.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v1 Swagger URL https://tourism.opendatahub.bz.it/swagger/index.html#/ODHActivityPoi/get_v1_ODHActivityPoi Sources LTS PoiData OpenData Pois data from LTS is partially closed data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RWIS Station</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/rwisstation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/rwisstation/</guid>
      <description>The Road Weather stations are sensors that measure both the road surface and the weather conditions. A22 (Modena - Brennero): restricted to a project
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v2 Swagger URL https://mobility.api.opendatahub.bz.it/ StationType RWISstation Sources A22 OpenData RWISstation data is partially closed data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Station</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/trafficstation_one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/trafficstation_one/</guid>
      <description>This dataset contains data collected by sensors along the Italian A22 motorway and municipality of Bolzano, such as, real time (A22) and aggregated data recorded by sensors drowned in asphalt, cameras, radar, other sensors.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v2 Swagger URL https://mobility.api.opendatahub.bz.it/ StationType TrafficSensor, Trafficstation Sources Municipality of Bolzano, A22 OpenData Data is partially closed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Velocity Sensors</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/linkstation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/linkstation/</guid>
      <description>Data processing of experimental Bluetooth-based sensors and detectors (A22 data based on Telepass). Gathered data are processed to obtain the estimated travel time and speed of the vehicles.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v2 Swagger URL https://mobility.api.opendatahub.bz.it/ StationType LinkStation Sources A22, NOI OpenData LinkStation data is partially closed data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weather</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/weather/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/weather/</guid>
      <description>This dataset contains meteorological data provided by the hydrographical Department of South Tyrol and Trentino, such as Precipitation and Air temperature. Here are the measurements of the weather data, not the forecast.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v2 Swagger URL https://mobility.api.opendatahub.bz.it/ StationType MeteoStation Sources Department of South Tyrol and Trentino OpenData MeteoStation data is partially closed data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weather Measuring Points</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/weather_measuringpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/weather_measuringpoint/</guid>
      <description>This dataset contains various Measuring Points with snow conditions provided by LTS.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v1 Swagger URL https://tourism.opendatahub.bz.it/swagger/index.html#/Weather/get_v1_Weather_Measuringpoint Sources LTS OpenData Measuring Points data is partially closed data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Webcam</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/webcam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/webcam/</guid>
      <description>This dataset contains Webcam Data. All data is synchronized daily from LTS and IDM (Webcam links).
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v1 Swagger URL https://tourism.opendatahub.bz.it/swagger/index.html#/WebcamInfo Sources Webcam links from LTS and IDM OpenData Webcam links data from IDM is open data. Data from LTS is partially closed data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accommodations Availability</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/accommodation_three/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/accommodation_three/</guid>
      <description>The Accommodation Endpoint offers the possibility to make an Availability Request. It can be done through HGV MSS (Booking Suedtirol Endpoint) or LTS. The Availability Request returns offers with room pricing. Availability requests on both sources are closed data.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json, XML AlpineBits API version v1, AlpineBits HotelData 2017-10, 2018-10 (soon 2020-10) Swagger URL https://tourism.opendatahub.bz.it/swagger/index.html#/Accommodation/post_v1_AccommodationAvailable AlpineBits URL https://alpinebits.opendatahub.bz.it/AlpineBits Sources Availability Requests provided by HGV/LTS OpenData Availability data is closed data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accommodations Rooms</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/accommodation_two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/accommodation_two/</guid>
      <description>On the Accommodations Endpoint it is also possible to get Rooms.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json, XML AlpineBits API version v1, AlpineBits HotelData 2017-10, 2018-10 (soon 2020-10) Swagger URL https://tourism.opendatahub.bz.it/swagger/index.html#/Accommodation/AccommodationRoomList AlpineBits URL https://alpinebits.opendatahub.bz.it/AlpineBits Sources Data provided by LTS / Availability Requests provided by HGV/LTS OpenData Rooms data is closed data </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Variable Message Sign</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/trafficstation_two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/traffic/trafficstation_two/</guid>
      <description>The VMS (Variable Message Sign) sensors collect data about the electronic road signs on the A22 motorway.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v2 Swagger URL https://mobility.api.opendatahub.bz.it/ StationType VMS Sources A22 OpenData Data only available to authorized collaborators </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Venue</title>
      <link>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/venue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/datasets/tourism/venue/</guid>
      <description>This dataset contains events location provided by LTS such as info about a location (e.g. number of seats, number of seats for disabled people, venue, etc.) or info to book an event location (e.g. prices, room configuration, etc.). Data are accessible in AlpineBits DestinationData format.
Output JSON, mime-type application/json API version v1 Swagger URL http://tourism.opendatahub.bz.it/swagger/index.html#/Venue Sources LTS OpenData Venue data is closed </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Components Store</title>
      <link>https://example.com/quickstart/web-components/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/quickstart/web-components/</guid>
      <description>Discover all the already developed Web Components. Freely available and ready to be reused.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobility API</title>
      <link>https://example.com/quickstart/swagger-mobility/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/quickstart/swagger-mobility/</guid>
      <description>Access swagger interface to browse data and learn how to use the Open Data Hub Mobility API.​</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tourism API</title>
      <link>https://example.com/quickstart/swagger-tourism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/quickstart/swagger-tourism/</guid>
      <description>Access swagger interface to browse data and learn how to use the Open Data Hub Tourism API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sparql endpoint</title>
      <link>https://example.com/quickstart/sparql/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/quickstart/sparql/</guid>
      <description>Access the rich high quality data by a flexible standards compliant query language. ​</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Graph</title>
      <link>https://example.com/quickstart/knowledge-graph/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/quickstart/knowledge-graph/</guid>
      <description>Access the browseable Knowledge Graph: data is presented as Linked Data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AlpineBits HotelData API</title>
      <link>https://example.com/quickstart/alpine-bits-hotel-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/quickstart/alpine-bits-hotel-data/</guid>
      <description>Access accommodation inventory data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AlpineBits DestinationData API</title>
      <link>https://example.com/quickstart/alpine-bits-destination-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/quickstart/alpine-bits-destination-data/</guid>
      <description>Access destination data such as mountain resorts, ski data and events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Documentation</title>
      <link>https://example.com/quickstart/read-the-docs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/quickstart/read-the-docs/</guid>
      <description>A collection of all technical resources about the Open Data Hub project. ​</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Source code repositories</title>
      <link>https://example.com/quickstart/git-hub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/quickstart/git-hub/</guid>
      <description>Access the NOI Techpark repositories to contribute or reuse code of the Open Data Hub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of HOWTOs</title>
      <link>https://example.com/quickstart/list-of-howtos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/quickstart/list-of-howtos/</guid>
      <description>A list of available howtos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2nd Open Data Hub Day</title>
      <link>https://example.com/events/11_odh_day_2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/events/11_odh_day_2022/</guid>
      <description>2nd Open Data Hub Day is a hybrid event about best practices to help you understand and get the most out of the world of data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity roundtable</title>
      <link>https://example.com/events/9_odh_aes_cybersecurityworkshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/events/9_odh_aes_cybersecurityworkshop/</guid>
      <description>Roundtable about Cybersecurity organized by Automotive Excellence Südtirol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mentor Final Event</title>
      <link>https://example.com/events/6_mentorfinalevent_20220126/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/events/6_mentorfinalevent_20220126/</guid>
      <description>Towards a Mobility-as-a-Service in rural alpine areas</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NOI Hackathon - Open Data Hub Edition</title>
      <link>https://example.com/events/10_odh_hackathon_2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/events/10_odh_hackathon_2022/</guid>
      <description>2 days, 24 hours, different topics to work on, one jury and amazing prizes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NOI Hackathon - Open Data Hub Edition</title>
      <link>https://example.com/events/4_odh_hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/events/4_odh_hackathon/</guid>
      <description>2 days, 24 hours, different topics to work on, one jury and amazing prizes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Data Hub Day - 2021</title>
      <link>https://example.com/events/3_odh_day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/events/3_odh_day/</guid>
      <description>Open Data Hub day is a hybrid event about best practices to help you understand and get the most out of the world of data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Developers&#39; Thursday | April</title>
      <link>https://example.com/events/8_sdt_20220407-mqtt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/events/8_sdt_20220407-mqtt/</guid>
      <description>Open Data Hub | MQTT broker and real-time flight data</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Developers&#39; Thursday | July</title>
      <link>https://example.com/events/12_sdt_20220707-webapi-sparql/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/events/12_sdt_20220707-webapi-sparql/</guid>
      <description>Open Data Hub | Accessing Web APIs as &amp;ldquo;Virtual&amp;rdquo; Relational Databases or Knowledge Graphs</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Developers&#39; Thursday | March</title>
      <link>https://example.com/events/7_sdt_20220303-databrowser/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/events/7_sdt_20220303-databrowser/</guid>
      <description>Open Data Hub | The new Data Browser</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>South Tyrol Free Software Conference</title>
      <link>https://example.com/events/5_sfscon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/events/5_sfscon/</guid>
      <description>The SFScon, is one the most established conferences and promotes the use of Free Software in digital infrastructures as a tool to achieve greater innovation and competitiveness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Webinar: How to create web components with Open Data Hub</title>
      <link>https://example.com/events/2_webinar3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/events/2_webinar3/</guid>
      <description>Participate in this webinar, and learn how to create web component for your website by visualising data from Open Data Hub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Webinar: How to use Open Data Hub for data analysis</title>
      <link>https://example.com/events/1_webinar2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/events/1_webinar2/</guid>
      <description>In this webinar, we will show you how to query the semantically integrated data on tourism and mobility stored in Open Data Hub for data analysis with R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Webinar: Why companies like Alperia and ACS use Open Data Hub</title>
      <link>https://example.com/events/0_webinar1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/events/0_webinar1/</guid>
      <description>What is Open Data Hub? And how could your company benefit from it?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
